in the previous video you saw how to
在之前的视频中你已经看到如何
【翻译/时间轴：庞伟 审核：AcceptedDoge】
compute derivatives and implement
计算导数和应用
gradient descent with respect to just
梯度下降在
one training example for logistic
logistic回归的一个训练样本上
regression now we want to do it for m
现在我们想要把它应用在m个
training examples to get started let's
训练样本上 首先 让我们
remind ourselves that the definition of
时刻记住有关于
the cost function J cost function (w,b)
损失函数J（w,b)的定义
which you care about is this average
它是1/m 乘上
right 1 over m sum from i equals 1 through m
求和从i等于1到m时的
you know the loss when your algorithm
这个损失函数L 当你的算法
output a^i on the example y well you
输出关于样本y的a^i
know a^i is the prediction on the I've
你知道 a^i是训练样本的预测值
trained example which is Sigma of z^i
也就是σ(z^i)
which is equal to Sigma of W transpose x^i
等于sigma作用于W的转置乘上x^i
plus b ok so what we show in the
加上b 所以 我们在
previous slide is for any single
前面的幻灯中展示的是对于任意单个
training example how to compute the
训练样本 如何计算微分
derivatives when you have just one
当你只有一个
training example great so dw1 dw2 and
训练样本 因此dw1 dw2和
db with now the superscript i to
db添上上标i
denote the corresponding values you get
表示你求得的相应的值
if you are doing what we did on the
如果你面对的是我们在
previous slide but just using the one
之前的幻灯中演示的那种情况 但只使用了一个
training example (x^i,y^i) excuse me
训练样本(x^i,y^i) 抱歉
I missing i there as well so now you
我这里少了个i 现在你知道
know the overall cost functions with the sum
带有求和的全局代价函数
was really the average of the 1
实际上是1到m项
over m term of the individual losses so
各个损失的平均 所以
it turns out that the derivative respect
它表明 全局代价函数
to say w_1 of the overall cost function
对w_1的微分
is also going to be the average of
也同样是
derivatives respect to w1 of the
各项损失对w_1微分的平均
individual loss terms but previously we
但之前我们
have already shown how to compute this
已经演示了如何计算
term as say (dw_1)^i right which we you
这项 也就是我所写的
know on the previous slide show how the
即之前幻灯中演示的如何
computes on a single training example
对单个训练样本进行计算
so what you need to do is really compute
所以你真正需要做的是计算
these own derivatives as we showed on
这些微分如我们在
the previous training example and
之前的训练样本上做的并且
average them and this will give you the
求平均 这会给你
overall gradient that you can use to
全局梯度值 你能够
implement straight into gradient decent so I know there was
把它直接应用到梯度下降算法中 所以 这里有
a lot of details but let's take all of
很多细节 但让我们把这些
this up and wrap this up into a concrete
装进一个具体的
algorithms and what you should implement
算法 同时你需要一起应用的
together just logistic regression with
就是logistic回归和
gradient descent working so just what
和梯度下降 因此你能做的
you can do let's initialize J equals 0
让我们初始化J等于0
um... dw_1 equals 0 dw_2 equals 0 db equals
dw_1等于0 dw_2等于0 db等于
0 and what we're going to do is use a
0 并且我们将要做的是使用一个
for loop over the training set and
for循环遍历训练集 同时
compute the derivatives to respect each
计算相应的每个
training example and then add them up
训练样本的微分 然后把它们加起来
all right so see as we do it for i
好了 如我们所做的让i
equals 1 through m so m is the number of
等于1到m m正好是
training examples we compute z^i equals W
训练样本个数 我们计算z^i等于
transpose x^i plus b um... the
W的转置乘上x^i 加上b
prediction a^i is equal to Sigma of z^i
a^i的预测值等于σ(z^i)
and then you know let's let's add up J
然后你知道 让我们加上J
J plus equals (y^i)log(a^i) um... plus 1 minus
J加等于(y^i)log(a^i)加上
y I log 1 minus a^i and then put a
(1-y^i)log(1-a^i) 然后加上一个
negative sign in front of the whole
符号在整个
thing and then as we saw earlier we have
公式的前面 然后如我们早前所见 我们有
dz^i or it is equal to a^i minus y^i and
dz^i或者它等于a^i减去y^i
dw gets plus equals (x_1)^i dz^i dw_2 plus
dw加等于(x_1)^i乘上dz^i dw_2加
equals (x_2)^i dz^i or and i'm doing this
等于(x_2)^i乘上dz^i 或者我正在做这个
calculation assuming that you have just
计算 假设你只有
the two features so the n is equal to 2
两个特征 所以n等于2
otherwise you do this for dw_1 dw_2 dw_3
否则你做这个从dw_1 dw_2 dw_3
and so on and db plus equals dz^i and I
一直下去 同时db加等于dz^i
guess that's the end of the for loop and
我想 这是for循环的结束
then finally having done this for all m
最终对所有的m个训练样本都进行了这个计算
training examples you will still need to
你还需要
divide by m because we're computing
除以m 因为我们计算
averages so dw_1
平均值 因此dw_1
divide equals m dw_2 divide equals m db
除等于m dw_2除等于m db
divide equals m in all the computed
除等于m 以平均的形式
averages and so with all of these
随着所有这些
calculations you've just computed the
计算 你已经计算了
derivative of the cost function J with
损失函数J
respect to each parameters w_1 w_2
对各个参数w_1 w_2
and b just come to details what we're
和b的微分 回顾我们正在做的细节
doing we're using dw_1 and dw_2 and db
我们使用dw_1 dw_2和db
to as accumulators right so that after
作为累加器 以至于这个计算之后
this computation you know dw_1 is equal
你知道dw_1等于
to the derivative of your overall cost
你的全局代价函数
function with respect to w_1 and
对w_1的微分
similarly for dw_2 and db so notice that
对dw_2和db也是一样 同时注意
dw_1 and dw_2 do not have a superscript i
dw_1和dw_2没有上标i
because we're using them in this code as
因为我们在这代码中把它们作为
accumulators to sum over the entire
累加器去求取整个
training set whereas in contrast dz^i
训练集上的和 相反的 dz^i
here this was um... dz with respect to
这是对应于
just one single training example that is
单个训练样本的dz 也就是
why that has a superscript i to refer to
为什么会有一个上标i指向
the one training example i that's
相应的第i个被计算的
computed on and so having finished all
训练样本 完成所有
these calculations to implement one step
这些计算后应用一步
of gradient descent you implement w_1
梯度下降 使得w_1
gets updated as w_1 minus a learning rate
获得更新 即w_1减去学习率
times dw_1 w_2 gives updates as w_2 minus
乘上dw_1 w_2更新即w_2减去
learning rate times dw_2 and b gets
学习率乘上dw_2 同时b
update as b minus learning rate times db
更新即b减去学习率乘上db
where dw_1 dw_2 and db where you know as
这里dw_1 dw_2和db 如你知道的被计算
computed and finally J here would also
最终这里的J也会
be a correct value for your cost
是你代价函数的正确值
function so everything on the slide
所以幻灯片上的所有东西
implements just one single step of
只应用了一步
gradient descent and so you have to
梯度下降 因此你需要
repeat everything on this slide multiple
重复以上内容很多次
times in order to take multiple steps of
以应用多次
gradient descent in case these details
梯度下降 看起来这些细节
seem too complicated
似乎很复杂
again don't worry too much about it for
但目前不要担心太多
now hopefully all this will be clearer
希望你明白 所有这些会变的更加清楚
when you go and implement this in the
当你继续尝试并应用这些在
programming assignment but it turns out
编程作业里 但它表明
there are two weaknesses with the
计算中有两个缺点
calculation as with as with implements
当应用在这里的时候
here which is that to implement
就是说应用此方法
logistic regression this way you need to
在logistic回归上你需要
write two for loops the first for loop
编写两个for循环 第一个for循环
is a small loop over the m training
是一个小循环遍历m个训练
examples and the second for loop is a
样本 第二个for循环是一个
for loop over all the features over here
遍历所有特征的for循环
right so in this example we just had two
这个例子中我们只有2个特征
features so n is equal to 2 and n_x
所以n等于2并且n_x
equals 2 but if you have more features
等于2 但如果你有更多特征
you end up writing your dw_1 dw_2 and
你开始编写你的dw_1 dw_2
you have similar computations for dw_3
你有相似的计算从dw_3
and so on down to dw_n so seems like you
一直下去到dw_n 所以看来你
need to have a for loop over the
需要一个for循环遍历
features over all n features
所有n个特征
when you're implementing deep learning
当你应用深度学习
algorithms, you'll find that having explicit
算法 你会发现在代码中显式地
for loops in your code makes your
使用for循环使你的
algorithm run less efficiency and so in
算法很低效 同时在
the deep learning area would move to a
深度学习领域会有
bigger and bigger data sets and so being
越来越大的数据集 所以能够
able to implement your algorithms
应用你的算法
without using explicit for loops is
且没有显式的for循环
really important and will help you to
会是重要的并且会帮助你
scale to much bigger data sets so it
适用于更大的数据集 所以
turns out that there are set of
这里有一些
techniques called vectorization
叫做矢量化技术
techniques that allows you to get rid of
它可以允许你的代码摆脱
these explicit full loops in your code I
这些显式的for循环
think in the pre deep learning era
我想在先于深度学习的时代
that's before the rise of deep learning
也就是深度学习兴起之前
vectorization was a nice to have you
矢量化是很棒的 可以使你
could sometimes do it to speed a vehicle
有时候加速你的运算
and sometimes not but in the deep
但有时候也未必能够 但是在
learning era vectorization that is
深度学习时代矢量化
getting rid of for loops like this and
即像这样摆脱for循环
like this has become really important
已经变得相当重要
because we're more and more training on
因为我们越来越多地训练
very large datasets and so you really
非常大的数据集 因此你真的
need your code to be very efficient so
需要你的代码变得非常高效 所以
in the next few videos we'll talk about
在接下来的几个视频中 我们会谈到
vectorization and how to implement all
矢量化以及如何应用这些
this without using even a single for loop
而连一个for循环都不使用
so of this I hope you have a sense
所以关于这些 我希望你有
of how to implement logistic regression
关于如何应用logistic回归
or gradient descent for logistic
或是用于logistic回归的梯度下降
regression um... things will be clearer
事情会变得更加清晰
when you implement the program exercise
当你进行编程练习
but before actually doing the program
但在真正做编程
exercise let's first talk about
练习之前 让我们先谈谈
vectorization so then you can implement
矢量化 然后你可以应用
this whole thing implement a single
全部这些东西 应用一个
iteration of gradient descent without
梯度下降的迭代而不使用
using any for loop
任何for循环